<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>

<!--
   New Perspectives on JavaScript, 2nd Edition
   Tutorial 12
   Case Problem 4

   The SF Control Room RSS Feed

   Filename:         sfpod.xml
   Supporting Files: 
-->

<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>The Sci-Fi Control Room Podcast</title>
        <description>Hugo and Nebula award-winning science fiction author Kevin Vinter
                     talks about the world of science fiction in the podcast. Join
                     Kevin twice-a-month for interviews, book reviews, and readings
                     from science fiction classics.
        </description>
        <link>http://www.sfcontrolroom.com/podcast.html</link>
        <language>en</language>

        <item>
            <title>Control Room #4</title>
            <description>Kevin looks at science fiction in the digital
                         age and the impact on online media on science
                         fiction magazines and fanzines. Kevin will also
                         read the first half of his new novelette,
                         Null Gateway.
            </description>
            <link>http://www.sfcontrolroom.com/podcast.html#sfcr04</link>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2012 18:39:14 -0800</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Control Room #3</title>
            <description>Kevin discusses the early days of the pulps with
                         science fiction historian, critic, and author,
                         Fredric Ogletree. Later, Kevin reads the winning
                         entries from the limerick contest. This month's
                         theme was: "Global Warming Limericks".
            </description>
            <link>http://www.sfcontrolroom.com/podcast.html#sfcr03</link>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2012 11:21:33 -0800</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Control Room #2</title>
            <description>Kevin reads an excerpt from his new novelette, The Wages of Sin,
                         and a science essay, I am an Emergent Phenomenom. Kevin
                         will also review the latests novel by K.D. Wilson and the
                         new sf movie, Blaster Force (it stinks).
            </description>
            <link>http://www.sfcontrolroom.com/podcast.html#sfcr02</link>
            <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2012 15:44:02 -0800</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Control Room #1</title>
            <description>Kevin Vinter introduces a new podcast with a packed program
                         of readings and interviews from the world of science fiction.
                         Kevin reads an extended excerpt from his Hugo awarding-winning
                         novel, The Long Sleep and provides backstory on the writing
                         of this sf classic. Join us for an interview with Otto
                         Greene, editor of Escher Magazine. Finally we'll look
                         at the recent WorldCon in Vancouver and applaud the winners.
            </description>
            <link>http://www.sfcontrolroom.com/podcast.html#sfcr01</link>
            <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2012 15:11:01 -0800</pubDate>
        </item>

    </channel>

</rss>

